<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>culture on Quantized Crow</title>
    <link>https://www.quantizedcrow.com/tags/culture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in culture on Quantized Crow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.quantizedcrow.com/tags/culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>David Berman: Amidst American Water, Part II</title>
      <link>https://www.quantizedcrow.com/posts/160321/amidst_american_water_ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quantizedcrow.com/posts/160321/amidst_american_water_ii/</guid>
      <description>The following is a partial transcription of a series of interviews conducted by Paula Crossfield with the late David Berman.
  Paula Crossfield: Before, we were talking about your process. In particular you were talking about &amp;ldquo;Smith and Jones&amp;rdquo; - looking at it as a way in to describing your writing process. You described working at The Whitney, and your twenty-lines-a-day, and having ten years&#39; worth of books. And then you started describing the actual nuts and bolts of how you were working on American Water so maybe we can go back to that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Berman: Amidst American Water, Part I</title>
      <link>https://www.quantizedcrow.com/posts/091220/amidst_american_water/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quantizedcrow.com/posts/091220/amidst_american_water/</guid>
      <description>The following is a partial transcription of a series of interviews conducted by Paula Crossfield with the late David Berman.
  Paula Crossfield: Hi, David?
David Berman: Hey Paula.
PC: Thank you so much for taking the time and for getting back to me so quickly.
DB: I was just reading about your Kickstarter campaign and I was wondering how it went?
PC: Well, we got it. We got $100,000 for our little food blog that I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on for 5 years and now I can make it a sustainable job, and hire somebody, and pay my writers which I&amp;rsquo;m really excited about!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
